Park Place, The Gallery of Art Research, Inc. and Paula Cooper Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Paula Cooper Gallery, 1962-2006, Series 3:; (Boxes 4-49, 51; 45.7 linear feet)
  - Artists' Files, 1962-2006, bulk mid-1970s-early 2000s, 3.3:
    - Campus, Peter (Box 24)
      - Biennale de Lyon, 1995-1997 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Kunsthalle Bremen, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Six Fragments (1976) [Printed Material], circa 1970s-1990s (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Anne-Marie Duguet, 1993-1995 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Divers, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Exhibition (Jan. 8 - Feb. 7, 1998), 1998 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Interface, Centre Pompidou, Kolnischer Kunstverein, 1989-1992 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Head of a Sad Young Woman (PC-10V) Video Installation, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Head of a Man With Death on His Mind (PC-11V), Coll: Bohen Foundation, circa 1970s- 1990s (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Kiva (PC-12V) Video Installation, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Mer (PC-13V) Video Installation, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Interface (PC-14V) Video Installation, Coll: Pompidou, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - Stasis (PC-15V) Video Installation, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Optical Sockets (PC-16V) Video Installation, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - Shadow Projection (PC-17V), Coll: Marlies Black Center for Studies, Bard College, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - Negative Crossing (PC-18V) Video Installation, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 24, Folder 21)
      - Anamesis (PC-19V) Video Installation, circa 1980s-1998 (Box 24, Folder 22)
      - col (PC-20V) Video Installation, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 24, Folder 23)
      - mem (PC-21V) Video Installation, Coll: Thomas Wegner, circa 1975-1990s (Box 24, Folder 24)
      - dor (PC-22V) Video Installation, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 24, Folder 25)
      - bys (PC-23V) Video Installation, circa 1976-1990s (Box 24, Folder 26)
      - sev (PC-24V) Video Installation, circa 1970s-1998 (Box 24, Folder 27)
      - cir (PC-25V) Video Installation, circa 1990s (Box 24, Folder 28)
      - aen (PC-26V) Video Installation, Coll: Bohen Foundation, circa 1990s (Box 24, Folder 29)
      - num (PC-27V) Video Installation, circa 1970s-1999 (Box 24, Folder 30)
      - lus (PC-28V) Video Installation, Coll: Thomas Wegner, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 24, Folder 31)
      - Photography Biennial, Rotterdam, Netherlands, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 32)
      - Pending, 1986-1989 (Box 24, Folder 33)
      - Weisser Raum, Hamburg, Germany, 1990-1992 (Box 24, Folder 34)
      - Whitney Museum Showing, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 35)
      - [Correspondence], 1986, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 36)
      - New Works Exhibition (Oct. 16 - Nov. 12, 1993), 1993 (Box 24, Folder 37)
      - Ascan Crone, Hamburg, Germany, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 38)
      - Divers, 1992-1994 (Box 24, Folder 39)
      - [Miscellaneous], circa 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 40)
      - Kunsthalle Wien, Vienna, Austria, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 41)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Exhibition Lists, circa 1980s (Box 24, Folder 42)
      - MIT Exhibition (1983), 1983 (Box 24, Folder 43)
      - "Black" Exhibition, Kunsthalle Dusseldorf, Germany, 1981, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 44)
      - Correspondence, 1978-1989 (Box 24, Folder 45)
      - Press Release, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 46)
      - Press (1977-1998) [Photocopies], circa 1977-1998, (4 folders) (Box 24, Folder 47-50)
      - Laminating and Mounting Information, 1990, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 51)
      - Everson Museum of Art Catalog, circa 1970s-1990s, (2 folders) (Box 24, Folder 52-53)
      - Photographic Materials, Available Works, circa 1980s-1998, (Oversized material housed in Box 51, Folder 3) (Box 24, Folder 54)
      - Photographic Materials, Artwork (1998), circa 1998 (Box 24, Folder 55)
    - Campus, Peter, Photographs (Box 24)
      - The Bohen Foundation Installation (1996-1997), circa 1996-1998 (Box 24, Folder 56)
      - Artwork (1997), circa 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 57)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Installation (Jan. 19 - Feb. 17, 1996), circa 1996-1998 (Box 24, Folder 58)
      - Artwork (1995), circa 1995-1998 (Box 24, Folder 59)
      - Artwork (1994), circa 1994-1998 (Box 24, Folder 60)
      - Installations (1993), circa 1993 (Box 24, Folder 61)
      - Artwork (1992), circa 1992-1998 (Box 24, Folder 62)
      - Artwork (1990), circa 1990-1998 (Box 24, Folder 63)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Installation (Oct. 3 - Nov. 2, 1991), circa 1991-1998 (Box 24, Folder 64)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Installation (Feb. 3-24, 1990), circa 1990-1998 (Box 24, Folder 65)
      - Computer Drawings and Paula Cooper Gallery Installation (1989), circa 1989-1998 (Box 24, Folder 66)
      - Artwork (1988), circa 1988-1998 (Box 24, Folder 67)
      - Galleria d'Arte Moderna Installation (May 28 - June 26, 1988), 1988 (Box 24, Folder 68)
      - Artwork (1987), 1987-1990s (Box 24, Folder 69)
      - Work Prints (1987), circa 1987 (Box 24, Folder 70)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Installation, Special Matte Finish (Sept. 9-30, 1987), 1988 (Box 24, Folder 71)
      - Artwork (1986), circa 1986-1990s (Box 24, Folder 72)
    - Campus, Peter, Photographs (Box 25)
      - Artwork Nos. 126-145 (1984), circa 1984-1990s, (2 folders) (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
      - Artwork (1982-1984), circa 1982-1990s (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Artwork (1982), circa 1982-1990s (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Installation (Mar. 4-28, 1981), circa 1981-1990s (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Artwork (1981), circa 1981-1990s (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Artwork (1980), circa 1980-1990s (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Installation (Jan. 16 - Feb. 7, 1979), circa 1979-1990s (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Leo Castelli Gallery (1973-1976), circa 1973-1990s (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Walker Art Center Installation (Sept. 30 - Nov. 18, 1979), circa 1979-1990s (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Artwork (1979), circa 1979-1990s (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Kolnischer Kunstverein Installation of mem, Cologne, Germany (1979), circa 1979-1990s (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Artwork (1978), circa 1978-1990s (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Artwork (pre-1977), circa 1970s-1990s (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Campus, Peter (Box 25)
      - Negatives [and Miscellaneous], circa 1970s-1990s (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Photo Projections, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Castoro, Rosemarie, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Dearing, James, circa 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Diao, David, 1969-1972 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Dobosen, Gary, circa 1970 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Fisher, Joel (Box 25)
      - Correspondence, 1971-1977 (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - Exhibitions, circa 1970-1975 (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - Photographs, 1970s (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Gilbert-Rolfe, Jeremy, 1977-1979 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Ginnever, Charles, circa 1970 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Ginnever, Charles, Louis Kahn's Comments on Ginnever's Sculpture, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Goldberg, Michael, Slides, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Hall, David, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Hollingworth, Keith, 1971-1975 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Hollingworth, Keith, Photographs, circa 1968-1973, (7 folders) (Box 25, Folder 30-36)
    - Huot, Robert, 1963-1979 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Hurson, Michael (Box 26)
      - Correspondence and Prices List, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Joe Fawbush Edition, 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Grenfell Press, circa 1990s (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - "The Last Home Show" (Fall 1992), circa 1992 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Dia, circa 1988-1992 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Robert Moskowitz Drawings, circa 1980s-1991 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Thurman Buzzard Essay, circa 1982 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - "Red and Blue" Play, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Exhibition List (Feb. 10 - Mar. 6, 1982), 1982 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, 1978-1985 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Clocktower Gallery, Chicago, IL (Feb. 23 - Mar. 25, 1984), 1984 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Petersburg Press, Inc., 1984-1987 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Jackson, Richard, circa 1977 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - James, Laurie, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Kirschenbaum, Bernard and George Kuehn, 1968-1972 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Kotik, Jan, 1970s-1984 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Kuehn, [George?] Gary, 1968-1972 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Kuehn, George (Box 26)
      - (Up to And 1970), circa 1969-1972 (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - Photographs of Box Piece (1969-1971), circa 1969-1971 (Box 26, Folder 19)
      - Photographs, circa 1971-1972, undated, (3 folders; Oversized material housed in Box 51, Folder 4) (Box 26, Folder 20-22)
    - Leavengood, David, Photographs, circa 1971, (Oversized materials housed in Box 51, Folder 5) (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Leonard, Zoe (Box 26)
      - Mouth open, teeth showing (ZL-51-SC) Documentation and Instructions, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence, 1992-2002, (6 folders) (Box 26, Folder 25-30)
    - Leonard, Zoe (Box 27)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Exhibition (Mar. 21 - Apr. 19, 2003), 2003 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Galerie Jennifer Flay, Paris, France, 1993-2001 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Exhibition (Oct. 21 - Nov. 25, 2000), 2000 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Creative Capital Grant, circa 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Baltimore Museum, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Sleuth Exhibition (June 1999), 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1998-2000 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - The Agency, London, England (Sept. 2002), 2002-2003 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Dye Transfer Prints Care, circa 1990s-2000s (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Herzliya Museum of Art, Israel, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Centre National de la Photographie, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Hamilton, Canada, 2001-2002 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Kunsthaus Glarus, Switzerland, 1995-1997 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Project Yankee, MassMoCA, MA, 2002-2003 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Paris Photo, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Gallery Anadiel, Jerusalem, Israel, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Christian Scheidemann, 1996-1999 (Box 27, Folder 17)
      - Vera Vita Gioia, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 18)
      - The Watermelon Woman at Groningen Museum, Netherlands, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 19)
      - Wiener Secession, 1995-1997 (Box 27, Folder 20)
      - Galerie Jennifer Flay, Paris, France, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 21)
      - Kunsthalle Basel, Switzerland, 1996-1997, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 22)
      - Nicholas Krups, Basel, Switzerland (June 2003), 2002 (Box 27, Folder 23)
      - Peter Pakesch, Basel Kunsthalle (Glarus/Vienna) [and Miscellaneous Correpondence], 1996- 1997 (Box 27, Folder 24)
      - Shoshana Wayne Gallery, Santa Monica, CA, 1994-1996 (Box 27, Folder 25)
      - Zanders, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 26)
      - The Fae Richards Photo Archive, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 27)
      - The Fae Richards Photo Archive, Artspace, San Francisco, CA, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 28)
      - The Fae Richards Photo Archive, Tate Modern, London, England (Oct. 2002), 2002 (Box 27, Folder 29)
      - The Watermelon Woman, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 30)
      - The Watermelon Woman Original Contracts, 1995-1997 (Box 27, Folder 31)
      - The Morgue (Pneumonia Death) by Andres Serrano, Ugo Ferranti Gallery, Rome, Italy, circa 1990s (Box 27, Folder 32)
      - Centre National d'Art Contemporain de Grenoble, France, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 33)
      - documenta und Museum Fridericianum, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Mangold, Robert (Box 27)
      - Exhibition Announcements, Postcards and Posters, 1983-1991, (4 folders) (Box 27, Folder 36-39)
      - [Works List], circa 1991 (Box 27, Folder 40)
      - Traveling Exhibition, 1984-1985 (Box 27, Folder 41)
      - The Baltimore Museum of Art, Baltimore, MD, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 42)
      - Brooke Alexander Sales, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 43)
      - Bonnefantenmuseum, Netherlands, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 44)
      - Damage (Dec. 1988), 1988-1989 (Box 27, Folder 45)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Exhibition Lists, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 46)
      - Cleveland Center for Contemporary Art Exhibition, Cleveland, OH, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 47)
      - "Robert Mangold: Frames of Reference", 1990 (Box 27, Folder 48)
      - New Work, undated (Box 27, Folder 49)
      - From John Weber Gallery, New York, NY, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 50)
      - New Works (1988), circa 1988 (Box 27, Folder 51)
      - Crown Point Press (1987), circa 1987 (Box 27, Folder 52)
      - Parasol Press (1988), circa 1988-1989 (Box 27, Folder 53)
      - Cooper & Alexander, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 54)
      - Correspondence, 1983-1988 (Box 27, Folder 55)
    - Mazzello, 161 Mulberry St., Slides, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Murray, Elizabeth (Box 28)
      - Exhibition Announcements and a Polaroid, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - [Administrative], 1987-1996 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Johnson County Community College, Kansas (Sept. 1993), 1991, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Print Retrospective to Travel, Barbara Krakow Gallery, Boston, MA, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Pending, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Wexner Center (Nov. 1991 - Feb. 1992), 1991 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Murrays Not in Show, circa 1980s (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Roberta Smith, "Motion Pictures" Drafts, circa 1980s (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Exhibition History, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - [Correspondence], 1988-1996, (2 folders) (Box 28, Folder 11-12)
      - Art Journal (Spring 1991), 1991 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - MTA Commission, New York, 1993-1995 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Museum of Modern Art, New York, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - Dallas Museum of Art Guest List, circa 1986 (Box 28, Folder 16)
      - Gallery Floor Plans, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - Harry N. Abrams, Inc., 1986 (Box 28, Folder 18)
      - MIT/Dallas Museum of Art, 1983-1987 (Box 28, Folder 19)
      - Kunstmuseum Luzern, Switzerland, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 20)
      - Carnegie-Mellon Exhibition (Oct. 25 - Dec. 13, 1986), 1986 (Box 28, Folder 21)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Exhibition List, 1981, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 22)
      - Portland Center for Visual Arts Exhibition, Portland, OR (1983), 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 23)
      - Return of the Sausages Agreement, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 24)
      - Knight Gallery Exhibition, Charlotte, NC (1984), 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence, 1975-1985 (Box 28, Folder 26)
      - Interview Transcripts, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 28, Folder 27)
      - MIT Interview Transcript, 1986, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 28, Folder 28-29)
      - David Nolan Gallery, New York, NY (1990), circa 1990 (Box 28, Folder 30)
      - Simca Print, circa 1982-1985 (Box 28, Folder 31)
      - Art Part Restoration Report, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 32)
      - Muscarelle Museum of Art, VA, 1990, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 33)
      - Prints, Derriere L'Etoile Studios, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 34)
      - Prints, Hand on Head, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 35)
      - Prints, Sanchez/Cooper & Alexander, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 36)
      - Mostly Mozart Print and Poster, 1980-1983 (Box 28, Folder 37)
      - ULAE Prints, 1986-1990 (Box 28, Folder 38)
      - Exhibition Announcements, Postcards and Posters, 1972-1996, (2 folders) (Box 28, Folder 39-40)
    - Murray, Elizabeth (Box 29)
      - Exhibition Announcements, Postcards and Posters, 1972-1996, (6 folders) (Box 29, Folder 1-6)
      - Press (1977-1995) [Photocopies], circa 1977-1990s, (11 folders) (Box 29, Folder 7-17)
      - Jeff Perrone Essay on Murray, circa 1992-1993 (Box 29, Folder 18)
      - Complete Biography, circa 1996 (Box 29, Folder 19)
      - Complete Bibliography, circa 1996 (Box 29, Folder 20)
      - Selected Bibliography, circa 1996 (Box 29, Folder 21)
      - Public Collections, circa 1996 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Murray, Elizabeth, Photographs (Box 29)
      - Gemini Prints Not at Gallery, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 23)
      - Paintings (1995), circa 1995 (Box 29, Folder 24)
      - Paintings (1994), circa 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 25)
      - Drawings and Installations (1994), 1994 (Box 29, Folder 26)
      - Gemini Prints at Gallery, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 27)
      - Drawings (1993), 1993 (Box 29, Folder 28)
      - Paintings (1993), 1993-1994 (Box 29, Folder 29)
      - Gemini G.E.L. Prints, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 30)
      - Drawings and Installations (1992), 1992 (Box 29, Folder 31)
      - Paintings (1992), circa 1992 (Box 29, Folder 32)
      - Paintings (1991), circa 1991-1996 (Box 29, Folder 33)
      - Drawings (1991), 1991, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 34)
      - Paintings (1990), circa 1989-1996 (Box 29, Folder 35)
      - Drawings (1990), circa 1989-1996 (Box 29, Folder 36)
      - Installations (1989), circa 1989-1990s (Box 29, Folder 37)
      - Paintings (1989), circa 1989-1996 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - Murray, Elizabeth, Photographs (Box 30)
      - Drawings (1989), circa 1988-1996 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Installations (Apr. - June 1988), 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Drawings (1988), circa 1987-1996 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Paintings (1988), circa 1987-1996 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Installation (Apr. 25 - May 23, 1987), circa 1987 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Drawings (1987), circa 1987-1996 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Paintings (1987), circa 1987-1996 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Drawings (1986), circa 1986-1996 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Paintings (1986), circa 1986-1996 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Paintings (1985), circa 1985-1996 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Drawings (1985), circa 1985-1996 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Drawings (1984), circa 1984-1996 (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Paintings (1984), circa 1984-1996 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Installation (Oct. 2-27, 1984), circa 1984 (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Drawings (1983), circa 1983-1996 (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - Paintings (1983), circa 1983-1996 (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - Drawings (1982), circa 1982-1996 (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - Paintings (1982), circa 1982-1996 (Box 30, Folder 18)
      - Photographic Materials and Printed Materials, 1980s-1990s (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - Installations (1981), 1981-1990s (Box 30, Folder 20)
      - Paintings (1981), circa 1981-1996 (Box 30, Folder 21)
      - Drawings (1981), circa 1981-1996 (Box 30, Folder 22)
      - Paintings (1980), circa 1980-1996 (Box 30, Folder 23)
      - Drawings (1980), circa 1980-1996 (Box 30, Folder 24)
      - Paintings (1979), circa 1979-1996 (Box 30, Folder 25)
      - Drawings (1979), circa 1979-1996 (Box 30, Folder 26)
      - Paintings (1978), circa 1978-1996 (Box 30, Folder 27)
      - Drawings (1978), circa 1978-1996 (Box 30, Folder 28)
      - Artwork (1977), circa 1977-1996 (Box 30, Folder 29)
      - Artwork (1976), circa 1976-1996 (Box 30, Folder 30)
      - Artwork and Installation (1975), circa 1975-1996 (Box 30, Folder 31)
      - Artwork and Installation (1974), circa 1974-1996 (Box 30, Folder 32)
      - Prints, circa 1982-1996 (Box 30, Folder 33)
      - Poloroids, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Murray, Elizabeth (Box 30)
      - Photographs and Transparencies, Changed Paintings, circa 1994-1996 (Box 30, Folder 35)
      - Negatives, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 30, Folder 36)
      - Negatives, Eeva-Inkeri, circa 1980s (Box 30, Folder 37)
      - Color Separations, circa 1980s (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Murray, Elizabeth, Transparencies (Box 30)
      - Paintings and Drawings (1995), circa 1995-1996 (Box 30, Folder 39)
      - Glass Pieces (1994), circa 1994-1996 (Box 30, Folder 40)
      - Paintings (1994), circa 1994-1996 (Box 30, Folder 41)
      - Drawings (1993), circa 1993-1996 (Box 30, Folder 42)
      - Paintings (1993), circa 1993-1996 (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - Murray, Elizabeth, Transparencies (Box 31)
      - Drawings (1992), circa 1992-1996 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Paintings (1992), circa 1992-1996 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Drawing 4x5 (1991), circa 1991-1996 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Paintings (1991), circa 1991-1996 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Paintings (1990), circa 1990-1996 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Drawings (1990), circa 1990-1996 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Installations (1990), circa 1990-1996 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Paintings (1989), circa 1989-1996 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Saatchi London Installation (Oct. 1988 - Feb. 1989), circa 1988-1996 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Drawings (1989), circa 1989-1996 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Paintings (1988), circa 1988-1996 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Whitney Museum of Art Exhibition, Extras, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Drawings (1988), circa 1988-1996 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Paintings (1987), circa 1987-1996 (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Drawings (1987), circa 1987-1996 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Murray, Elizabeth, Transparencies (Box 32)
      - Paintings (1986), circa 1986-1996 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Drawings (1986), circa 1986-1996 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Drawings (1985), circa 1985-1996 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Paintings (1985), circa 1985-1996 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Drawings (1984), circa 1984-1996 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Paintings (1984), circa 1984-1996 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Drawings (1983), circa 1983-1996 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Paintings (1983), circa 1983-1996 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Paintings (1982), circa 1982-1996 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Drawings (1982), circa 1982-1996 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Paula Cooper Gallery Installation (May 1-30, 1981), 1980s-1990s (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Drawings (1981), circa 1981-1996 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Paintings (1981), circa 1981-1996 (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Paintings (1980), circa 1980-1996 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Artwork (1978-1979), circa 1978-1996 (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Artwork (1976-1977), circa 1976-1996 (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - Artwork (Pre-1976), circa 1970s-1996 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Prints, circa 1984-1996 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Murray, Robert, 1974-1977, 1984, (2 folders) (Box 32, Folder 19-20)
    - Murray, Robert, 1974-1977, 1984, (2 folders) (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
    - Noland, Cady (Box 33)
      - Louisiana Museum of Modern Art, Denmark, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - American Fine Arts Dispute, circa 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 33, Folder 4-5)
      - Correspondence, 1992-1997, (2 folders) (Box 33, Folder 6-7)
      - John Silberman, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Certificates of Authenticity, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - SFMOMA Pricing, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Ron McPherson Estimates, Bills, Etc., 1994 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Agreements With Paula Cooper Gallery, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Museum Boymans-van Beuningen, Rotterdam, Netherlands, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - Dragoslav Scepanovic, 1994-1995, (2 folders) (Box 33, Folder 14-15)
      - Press (1989-1994) [Photocopies], circa 1989-1995, (3 folders) (Box 33, Folder 16-18)
      - Complete Biography, circa 1994 (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - Complete Bibliography, circa 1994 (Box 33, Folder 20)
      - [Correspondence], circa 1989-1995, (2 folders) (Box 33, Folder 21-22)
    - Phelan, Ellen, circa 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Pinchbeck, Peter, Slides, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Piper, Adrian, Correspondence, 1992-2004, (3 folders) (Box 33, Folder 25-27)
    - Piper, Adrian (Box 34)
      - Correspondence, 1992-2004, (2 folders) (Box 34, Folder 1-2)
      - Inventory, 2003-2004 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Retrospective, 2001-2004, (2 folders) (Box 34, Folder 4-5)
      - Exhibition Agreement and Original Transfer of Work of Art, 1997-1998 (Box 34, Folder 6)